Morning.
- Hey there.
- Good morning.
- Hi, girls.
- Ladies.
- Are we sitting randomly again?
- Morning.
Morning.
- What's up?
- Hey, Rune.
You look cute today too.
MIMI (29)
HOSTESS
SHARAN (21)
LOUNGE HOSTESS
- Have you drawn portraits?
- Not yet.
- I drew you, Mimi.
- I heard the drawing was of a guy.
You did?
- I started drawing yours.
- Yeah?
- It's a rough sketch.
- Yeah.
A transfer student
will now be joining you.
- Wait.
- That's crazy.
- No way.
- What?
- Huh?
- Who's that?
- Hello.
- Hey there.
- Hey.
- That surprised me.
- I'm Kaho Chinen, the transfer student.
- A student? At this stage?
- Now? Out of nowhere?
- That's crazy.
- What's happening?
- Oh, my gosh. Have a seat.
- Yeah, please.
- May I?
- Wild.
My name is Kaho Chinen.
I'm 20, and I work at a hostess bar.
I'm popular.
KAHO CHINEN
AKA KAHOCHI (20)
When I was, like, 17 years old,
I got arrested
for possession of marijuana.
I came out of the bathroom,
and I was surrounded by the cops.
My dad was super strict, so I rebelled.
After I ran away from home,
I started hanging out with people
who were a couple years older than me.
Everyone was into marijuana.
That's how it started for me.
Some people think
I have a thing for unattractive guys.
I've been cheated on.
This Noh mask and Hannya mask
represent a story.
It's about getting cheated on
and turning into a Hannya.
I thought, "That's me."
Plus, I'd always wanted
traditional Japanese tattoos.
I want to find my future husband.
And I want to win it all.
Her left arm is kind of scary.
- A transfer student at this point?
- Um, nice to meet you all.
- All of a sudden?
- Kahochi?
Kahochi.
- Okinawa?
- I'm from Okinawa.
- Really? Okinawa?
- Oh, she's from Okinawa.
Looks like Maru's perked up.
- No way.
- Wow, unreal.
- That's so crazy.
- I'm 20 years old.
- That's it?
- You're 20?
- And I work at a hostess bar.
- Wow, that's wild.
- A bar in Okinawa?
- We're the same age!
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's right.
I can't take this.
- It's so frustrating.
- That looks cool.
Let's introduce ourselves.
- Yes, great.
- Thanks.
- Go this way?
- We forget too.
- You be the MC.
- We have an MC.
- Start.
- Here we go.
Hey, can I step out for a second?
I just can't.
Huh? What's up?
Wait.
Oh, sorry. Sharan!
What'd I do?
- Did I do something?
- No.
- Me?
- Me.
- Let's introduce ourselves.
So, there's a lot going on,
but, anyway, good morning.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello, Kahochi.
- I'm pissed. So annoyed.
- What happened?
- Tai-chan's pissing me off.
- But why?
- Why? He's annoying.
- How? Is it how he's acting?
- I'm so upset.
- I hear you.
- He's the worst.
- Hey, stay strong.
Come on, it's okay.
You're okay, don't cry.
He's seriously annoying.
- He's just being so obvious.
- Yeah.
- Tai-chan.
- Right.
- You know? Do you see it?
- See how he's acting?
Wouldn't you hate it
if the person you liked acted like that?
Yeah.
- I feel like he doesn't talk to me.
- Right.
I was about to lose it
and lash out at him,
- but I thought that'd be bad.
- Yeah.
It's just so frustrating.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- I almost went off. Seriously.
- Mmm…
I just get so jealous
about stuff like that.
The reason I'm this mad
is because I like him so much.
- But you're keeping it to yourself.
- Yeah.
- That's why I thought I should leave.
- I see.
He's the worst, seriously.
So, what now? Everyone's waiting for us.
If you stay out here longer…
- Okay.
- …it will just get awkward.
So just hold it in for now.
Let's go back in. Okay?
Hmm. You good?
Should I take it out
on the transfer student?
No.
- You're right.
- Mmm.
You might change Tai-chan's mind.
You probably want to avoid that.
- Mmm.
- I'm here for you, though.
Let's go back.
I think I like him too much.
So intensely that I want to cry, for real.
It's so tough.
Love hurts so bad.
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RUGGED APPRENTICE TATTOO ARTIST
DRAWN TO TATTOOS' SEX APPEAL
KAZUMA
KABUKICHO HOST BOSS
WHO WANTS TO GET SERIOUS ABOUT LOVE
MARU
IBARAKI HOSTESS WITH A BIKE CREW
LOOKING FOR A HUSBAND
AYACHERU
GYARU HOSTESS FROM MIYAGI
A TSUNDERE WHO HATES TO LOSE
RINRIN
KITASHINCHI BAR OWNER
WHO'S ALL ABOUT THE VIBES
RYOPI
WILD OKINAWAN NAIL ARTIST
WITH A PHOENIX ON HER BACK
SARA
FUKUSHIMA HOSTESS
WHO CHARGES INTO LOVE HEAD-FIRST
SHARAN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
EDOGAWA RAPPER
SEEKING LOVE WITH HONOR
RUNE
KITASHINCHI'S NO.1 HOSTESS
BLEEDING BIG-SIS ENERGY
MIMI
STRAIGHT-SHOOTING FORMER MMA CHAMP
KAMAKEN
POPULAR OKINAWAN HOSTESS LOOKING FOR LOVE
KAHOCHI
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON LOVE
We're back.
- Welcome back.
- Oh, good.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Good?
- We were introducing ourselves.
Ready to say your name?
Hmm? What do I say?
Your name and…
- Name, age, occupation, your type.
- I only have one of those.
Yeah.
- Let's go.
- So, my name is Sharan,
and I'm 21 years old.
- And I work at a lounge.
- Mmm-hmm.
Nice to meet you.
Rinrin, 20.
I work at a bar, a hostess bar.
- What else?
- Your type.
My type?
I like someone who is manly
and fun to be with. Yeah.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
- All right!
- Great.
What else?
RYOPI (29)
BAR OWNER
- Her type, how about that?
- Good idea.
- What kind of guy do you like?
- My type is, mmm, chubby.
- Wait, what?
- Chubby, that's you!
- That's him!
- Go, Kazuma!
- Let's go!
- Yes!
There we go.
Yeah, finally.
Kazuma looks so happy.
Kazuma! Your time to shine!
My time? Has it finally come?
KAZUMA (26)
PART-TIMER
Congrats!
Kazuma!
- Chubby, and?
- Chubby, and…
Mmm, a manly guy.
It's Kazuma!
- That's Kazuma!
- Hey.
- What?
- Sounds like something's coming.
- What is it?
- Seriously?
Let's prepare for the welcome party
to celebrate the transfer student.
Alcohol is allowed today.
Yes!
Here we go! Yes, yes, yes!
LOVE DINER
- Who cut these carrots?
- That was Maru.
- I got it.
- Maru!
- We making curry?
- Yeah?
These carrots you cut are curry-sized,
stir-fry is smaller.
Can I try some?
Hold each lengthwise and cut it like this.
- Let me try.
- So, half?
- No, into threes.
- Just one bite.
- That would be three.
- Into three pieces?
- They need to be thinner.
- Okay. Like this?
Don't forget this one.
- Yeah, that's it.
- Ah, got it.
- Good job.
- I can do it if I just try.
He's actually kind of cute, that Maru.
He's now showing his human side.
Honestly, I don't get it.
I wasn't sure what that was all about,
why you walked out of the room.
- I mean, I messed up.
- You know, I thought-- What?
- It was mistake.
- What do you mean?
I wanted to apologize,
but I felt like I couldn't.
I feel super bad about it, for real.
I think I need to change.
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
I lose my temper so easily.
- Mmm.
- Rinrin knows what I'm like.
But I'll try not to cry anymore.
- It hurts.
- Yeah.
I'm such a crybaby, I know.
I think this school
is all about personal growth.
- I'm still growing too.
- Do you think I can change?
Mmm… I mean, hey, I did.
Like I said, the people I met in Part 1,
they taught me a lot.
Mmm…
It's painful.
- Maybe I should quit.
- Seriously. It hurts.
I love you so much, it hurts.
Honestly.
It hurts so much that
I wanted to quit this school completely.
I see.
Whenever I fall for someone,
I fall too hard. Seriously.
Is Mimi someone
you're actually interested in?
- She is.
- Do I even have a chance?
I think I want to talk to Mimi more first.
It hurts.
I know that I can come on
too strong sometimes.
It hasn't changed?
I'm still interested in her.
I hate this.
I hate that I'm like this.
- Seriously.
- Should we go back?
I'm heading back. I'm gonna go help.
It hurts.
I mean, am I actually
in the wrong on this?
Seeing Sharan cry that much
honestly made me wonder
if I should actually feel responsible
for all that.
Like, maybe it was my fault,
maybe I did something wrong.
I mean, I definitely liked hearing
that she likes me so much.
But even if she keeps
feeling that way about me,
I don't know what to do anymore.
Right now, there's someone else
I need to focus on.
I've already told her that it's Mimi.
Ryopi's got something to say.
Right. Everyone, have a seat.
- Sit for a second.
- Stop, that's not funny.
Okay, so let me just say something.
- What?
- I promise, I'm not mad or anything.
I don't want anyone
to take this the wrong way, but…
Sharan's birthday is coming up,
so we should make a cake for her, right?
That's so funny! He totally got me!
- For real.
- Jeez! People from Kansai are funny.
Right?
- Sounds good. Let's do it.
- You're good!
- He got us.
- That was good.
And Rinrin just had
her coming-of-age ceremony,
so we should make a cake for her too.
- We can celebrate everyone together.
- Wait.
- Sweet!
- Did you have it too?
- The more the merrier!
- I did. I had my ceremony.
- Yay!
- It's going to be so much fun.
Let's all make a cake together.
- Yeah, day after tomorrow.
- Sounds good.
All right. Okay.
Everyone, grab your glasses. Here we go.
- Do you want to say something?
- Right. Okay, let's go.
Okay, then here we go.
I look forward to getting to know you all.
- Cheers!
- This is great!
- Cheers, cheers, everyone. Cheers.
- Okay, cheers.
We have prepared
some one-on-one time for you,
ahead of tomorrow's overnight date.
Specifically, for the transfer student,
please try talking one-on-one
with a few men in the group.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
No worries. I'm fine.
You've got traditional tattoos,
I like that a lot.
- Yeah? I really like traditional.
- Yeah.
I was born in Japan, so I wanted to go
with something Japanese.
I see. What do you have?
This is half Hannya mask,
and the other half is a Noh mask.
Plus, a bonji and cherry blossoms.
Cherry blossoms are beautiful.
I've got cherry blossoms too.
- Really?
- Probably a different color.
What color is it?
- Pink. Yeah, for sure.
- Pink? Nice.
- But red looks good too. Looks classy.
- Yeah.
- And blue bonji?
- I had it done in blue.
- Wow. That's rare.
- Yeah.
- It was tough to choose the color.
- Right.
- But I decided to go with blue.
- Blue bonji is nice.
- First time I've seen it.
- Right?
The tattoo stands out more
because you've got fair skin.
So there are still a lot more tattoos
that I want to get.
Hmm?
But I gained weight, so I'm going to wait
until I lose some first.
- Gained weight? But you're so thin.
- I gained a lot.
I'm the fat one. When I put on a swimsuit,
my belly spills over.
But I think chubby guys
are more attractive. I tell everyone that.
Mmm.
- So…
- Wait, why?
I mean, super skinny guys
just don't seem manly.
They look weak. I don't like guys
who look weak. They seem wimpy.
- So you like guys who look strong.
- Yeah, yeah. For sure.
- Like, manly?
- Mmm-hmm, yeah.
Whenever I like someone,
I keep telling them, "Eat more,"
and I end up fattening them up.
I eat a ton, actually.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm. I'm always eating.
I prefer guys who eat a lot
over guys who hardly eat.
Same goes for women.
It's nice when they eat well, you know?
Exactly. That's what people tell me,
and then I gained weight.
- I see.
- Now I don't know how to lose the weight.
- They're a good match, right?
- Yeah.
SMOKERS' LOUNGE
- Kaho.
- You aren't smoking?
I am.
So I was going to tell everyone earlier…
I have a kid.
- Yeah, I have a kid.
- What?
Yeah, I was going to say it
when I first came in…
- Right.
- …but my mind just went blank.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- How old were you when you had it?
- 17.
- Oh, so your kid's 3 now?
- That's right.
- You're a single mother?
- Yeah, single mom.
I see. Did your husband leave you?
He wasn't my husband or anything.
We were dating when I was 17,
but we broke up, and that was that.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mmm-hmm.
When I was 16 years old,
I started dating a guy the same age as me.
I got pregnant by him,
and had my kid after I turned 17.
I used to smoke weed, but I quit.
I quit everything.
If I hadn't given birth to my child,
I think I would have…
probably lost my mind. For sure.
My parents have both been
super supportive of me coming here
and doing this show.
They're looking after my kid
while I'm here.
Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
Since I have a kid,
I want someone who is serious enough
to think about getting married.
I am not at all that interested
in dating a person
who's just looking to have fun.
So our transfer student
that just arrived, Kahochi,
- we just learned she has a child.
- Yeah.
Her parents said they would help
take care of her child for her
if she wanted to come on Badly In Love.
So that's the kind of show this is now?
We're like Kohaku.
Yeah, I guess we're one of those shows
parents actually want their kids to be on.
- This kind of genre.
- Yes.
- We're the Kohaku of this genre now.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- So her parents are watching?
Of course, they're watching.
- Hello, thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Your daughter's doing great. Yes.
- She's in good hands, so don't worry.
- Your daughter's good.
LOVE DINER
- Let's go.
- Okay, over here.
All right.
Okay, so…
I've kind of decided to just keep talking
- to the same girl around school.
- Okay.
There's a girl who keeps telling me that
she wants to spend time together,
and talk to me.
And, you know, I genuinely
feel comfortable around her,
and I think she's great.
But since coming to this school,
there hasn't been anyone
- that I wanted to make the first move on.
- Mmm.
And then, you showed up to the school.
Mmm-hmm.
Now, I want to make a move on you.
- I've had my eye on you the most.
- For real?
When I see you talking to the other girls,
to me at least, it seems like
you're kind of all over the place.
- No way.
- Honestly.
I want to be the only girl you look at.
Okay, so you think of me that way too.
Yeah, I do. For sure.
- For real?
- I do.
But when it seems like
you can't decide who you like,
it doesn't sit right with me.
Well, I decided that for the second half,
I'm just going to be honest
about what I want. I'll speak my mind.
- Hmm.
- Mmm.
And what I want is to talk to you.
Mmm-hmm.
- Aya's willing to do I want to do.
- So if you win tomorrow's overnight date,
- who would you choose to take on it?
- You.
- I'm so happy.
- For sure.
- I'd definitely ask you.
- I thought,
"What kind of challenge will it be?"
- Exactly.
- Cooking?
Or running. If it is, you're fast, right?
Whatever it is, I'll give it 100%. Yeah.
- But it is a competition.
- Of course.
- Excuse me.
- Hey.
- Oh, Rune.
- It's Rune again.
- Rune again.
- His timing is so great.
Hey, give me a palm reading too.
Maru, you mind if I talk to her a bit?
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- You guys have it easy.
- Thanks.
- I'm glad we got to talk.
- Yeah.
- I'll ask you on the date.
- I'll be waiting.
No. I'll ask her, so back off.
I honestly didn't think
you'd come talk to me, so I'm glad.
Why not? Of course, I would.
- No, you almost didn't.
- But I did.
- Yesterday in the girls' room--
- I did come.
Hold on a sec, can I be honest with you?
We were saying you're the hardest to read.
- Really? You think that?
- Yeah.
Well, you're sort of nice to everyone.
You are, that's definitely true.
And because you are nice to everyone,
- none of us know who you're interested in.
- Yeah.
I can tell you genuinely give
all of us girls an equal chance,
and that's great,
but that makes you the hardest to read.
When it comes to romance,
I think it's a bit different.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
- What kind of girl do you like?
- Mimi.
Wait, why is that?
- Why?
- Yeah.
Mmm…
- You're not just feeling sorry for me?
- No, I'm not.
- You're not?
- No.
- Right now, everyone is at a zero.
- Uh-huh.
And you are at 100.
Wait, but the new girl, she's so cute.
- I mean, sure.
- And she's 20.
But she's younger than my sister.
And so, actually…
I don't know, I feel like
I see her more as a little sister
- than someone I'd like.
- Well, I mean, coming from a superhero…
Honestly, I don't see her
as a romantic interest at all.
- Hmm. Really?
- Yeah.
So who would you pick for a date?
- Mimi. Mmm-hmm.
- For real?
All right.
- Oh, Tai-chan.
- Glad I'm the last one here.
So how was it?
- "How was it?"
- Talking to the other guys.
- "Talking to the other guys?"
- How was it talking with them?
Well… I don't know.
- You really don't know?
- No.
Guess I'm just wondering how they'll show
their manly side tomorrow.
I think that'll be easy.
- I'm hoping for the best.
- You are?
- Of course, I am.
- And that's me?
If you win,
who would you pick for the date?
- So she's asking everyone? Wow.
- Yep.
Sorry, but to be honest,
you're the one I'd take.
Once I lock in,
there's no stopping me.
I mean, I'll say it again. Mmm.
You're the one I choose, Mimi.
- I'm so happy.
- Yeah.
This is the first time in my entire life
I've actually tried to make a guy
romantically interested in me.
So, right now, my head's kind of a mess.
I mean, you know,
I'm a professional hostess after all.
So it might seem like
I'd be pretty good at this kind of thing.
But when it comes to romance,
it's new to me.
When someone's interested,
I try to give them a chance, but…
I can't--
I don't know, it all feels fake.
I'm not even sure what to think anymore.
This is my favorite spot.
- For real? It's my first time. Yeah.
- Really?
Well, tomorrow, finally,
- one of us guys get to choose.
- Yeah.
- So can you?
- Can I what?
- Can you win? Confident?
- Tell me.
- I'll win. I will, yes.
- Oh, yeah?
So tell me straight,
who are you most interested in right now?
- Most interested in?
- Yeah.
- I'm curious.
- Well…
Mmm, if I had to be totally honest
right now, I'd say it was you.
Okay, but if it comes to the date,
will you be inviting me?
What's with that awkward smile?
Seriously.
- Mmm…
- No?
I see how it is. You had to ask.
- Yeah.
Hmm…
Well, I'm going for the win tomorrow.
Mmm.
And there is someone else
that I want to ask.
Mmm.
I mean, I told her that earlier today.
- Isn't this cruel?
- Oh, man.
Mimi?
Mmm.
Okay, I see.
- I told her that.
- I get it.
- Then, I'll do that.
- If that's the case, I'm good. Yeah.
- What do you mean?
- Mmm…
Mmm, okay.
- You okay?
- What? Hmm?
Well, I'm rooting for you.
That's it.
Do you mean, like, "Whatever"?
- Mmm.
- Okay.
- Yeah. I see.
- Mmm.
- That's what I was thinking.
- Hmm.
I mean, I'm glad that you told me.
So now I know.
- See you tomorrow?
- Mmm.
- Good night.
- Night.
- Thank you. Yeah.
- Have a good night.
So heartbreaking.
SMOKERS' LOUNGE
This is so annoying.
Men just say whatever they want.
I'm so pissed off right now.
I'll go after this cigarette, yeah.
Go ahead, don't wait for me.
- No, we gotta go now.
- Hey, we gotta go.
But can I at least have a smoke first?
- No, we don't have time.
- Yeah, they're waiting for us.
Smoke after we're done.
What? Why'd you say it like that?
- Who are you talking to?
- Let's go.
- Not everything has to be a thing.
- Enough. This is so annoying.
- Who are you talking to?
- Do it.
- I'm for real. Bring it, then. Go on.
- Don't threaten me.
- That's enough.
- Just do it.
- What's with you?
- Quit egging her on!
- Come on, then!
- I don't feel provoked at all.
- Not in front of the transfer.
- Hey, just go in with Aya. Go ahead.
- What's her problem?
- Let's go.
- How old are you?
Aya.
I get it.
I know you've got a lot you want to say
and I know you're pissed too.
But the transfer student
needs to see our room.
You said you get it,
but whose side are you on?
- Hmm? There are no sides.
- Whose side are you on?
- Then what?
- Don't give me, "Then what?"
- There are no sides.
- Okay.
- Let's act normal for now. Let's go in--
- Then why were you holding her back?
No, no. Now's not the time to fight.
Is she still talking out here?
- I'll say what I want.
- You don't have to do that.
- Get over here!
- That's enough.
- Come here!
- You don't need to do this.
Okay, let's do this.
- Stop, we have a transfer student here.
- You're acting like a child.
Let's just talk it out.
Everyone has something to say.
If you're that upset,
let's go talk over there.
Fine, whatever.
- What?
- Take it easy, okay?
Don't do that.
Why are you taking it out on Mimi?
- No, she's not doing that.
- I'm not taking it out on her.
- You wanna go?
- You started it!
- That's enough!
- Hey!
- Okay, okay.
- That's what I should be saying.
- What? We can see it in your face!
- That's enough.
- Then come at me. Try me.
- You're a brat!
You're 24, and make faces like a child.
You're so lame.
- My age has nothing to do with this.
- What?
So let's go. Come and get it, then.
- Stop.
- Just stay calm down and talk it out.
- Please just chill.
- I'm so pissed.
- That's it, I quit.
- Why are you saying that?
- No, I'm done with this.
- Why are you saying that? Tell me.
If talking it out doesn't change
your mind, then I won't stop you.
- Mmm.
- So let's just talk about it.
- For what?
- Take a breath first.
- I'm just tired of this.
- I get it.
Just think about it first. Let's talk.
- Let's see this through together.
- Can I go home?
You being here
makes me feel like I can keep going.
You're the reason
I made it this far. Okay?
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
Sometimes, I just wish
I was a stronger woman.
Hey, come on.
You don't have to wish
that you were someone else. You don't.
- You're fine the way you are.
- Rune!
For real.
Mmm.
There are still things
I want to do together with you,
and feelings I want to figure out.
I know that
I'll regret it, too, if you leave.
Mmm.
- Thanksies.
- No problem.
I'm the one who should be thanking you
from day one.
- Thank you so much.
- Oh, man.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go, let's do this.
- Thank you.
- Welcome back.
- Yeah, welcome back.
I'm sorry about today.
I know that I probably ruined the mood.
I'm sorry too. I knew something
must have happened when you came back.
You seemed upset.
I think I should've, you know,
given you a little more time
and more space
to process everything
that you were feeling in that moment.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry too.
You know, for pushing you and all that.
I feel bad.
But as we talked,
I realized I was at fault too,
for letting so much of what I was feeling
- show in my facial expressions.
- Okay.
So I wanted to apologize for that.
Seriously.
I'm very sorry.
Well, we have the overnight date tomorrow.
Let's move forward
and focus on the guys. Okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- No, you're fine.
- Well, so much just happened.
- Oh, man, it sure did!
Who would've thought
we would see the security team
- break up a girls' fight on the show?
- A first for the girls.
So Ayacheru and Maru were talking,
that's when she found out that Maru
was going to ask Mimi on the date.
Still reeling from that,
she went to the smoking area,
- then Rinrin came at her pretty hard.
- Yeah.
All that fighting was set in motion
by that initial exchange between them.
- And then, "Thanksies."
- Yeah, "Thanksies."
- "Thanksies."
- She's got a way with words!
She sure does.
She comes up
with more killer lines than rappers.
She does.
"To tell you straight," and "Thanksies."
- Ayacheru is the best.
- And Mimi…
So she made three guys in a row
say that if they win,
they'll ask her on the date tomorrow.
-Looked like they were in a hostess bar.
- It really was.
But it's like, she's confused
about her own feelings
- because she does stuff like this.
- Maybe it's a habit left over from work.
So she's able to do something like that,
but emotionally,
she might not have that much experience
having to deal with her true feelings
in real romantic relationships.
- But guys can't tell the difference.
- That is so true.
I can tell that Tai-chan
doesn't really stand a chance.
- Yeah.
- You don't think?
I know I'm just a guy, but, yeah.
You know, unless there's a major twist,
I actually don't think
- he has a chance either.
- Hmm.
- There it is, the prison.
- Yeah, for real.
That's what it looks like, right?
What is he doing?
- Morning.
- Hey.
Oh, morning.
- So the girls talked it out.
- We have something we want to say.
Yesterday, at the end of the night,
a few of us got into a big fight,
and then, everyone came out to help us,
and heard everything,
so we wanted to apologize about that.
And also, we wanted to thank you
for helping us out, so…
- The girls caused trouble, we're sorry.
- It's okay.
And thank you. It helped you were there.
- Thank you so much.
- Were you able to make up?
- Yes.
- We did.
- That's what matters most.
- Right, Aya?
It's Ethics class again.
Life begins when you stop running away
from your past.
Please reflect on the mistakes
you have made
and discuss them amongst yourselves.
This time, it's Kahochi.
- Okay.
- Please go ahead.
All right.
I will tell my story.
- You can do it.
- Good luck, do your best.
First of all,
my father was very strict.
Yeah, when I was in middle school,
he was very serious about curfews.
And I think that just made me
want to rebel even more.
So pretty soon, I started
to get into all kinds of trouble.
And, like, I got arrested
for possession of marijuana.
My dad is a huge worrywart,
and we ended up getting into a fight.
He told me to get out of the house,
so I left and ran away from home
for two months.
And then my mom told me
that my dad was worried about me,
and that I should come home.
But, like, I was still
getting into more trouble.
Then I finally went back.
At the time, my dad seemed
very apologetic about it, you know.
I said I'm sorry for running away.
And then, like, at the time…
we talked it out with each other.
I made him…
…go through a lot, like,
with people at his work and everything.
Mmm.
He worried that people would think…
Oh, what's wrong?
When I got arrested by the police, like,
he didn't even yell at me.
He just scolded me quietly.
Mmm.
- Look what she's doing.
- Thanks.
That's nice of her. Yeah.
I know I'm still a burden on them,
and I'm, like, so sorry about that.
I feel the most sorry
for my dad, honestly.
And then, when I was 16,
I had a boyfriend,
I got pregnant and had a baby.
And we weren't married.
We broke up before I turned 18.
I couldn't raise the baby on my own,
so my dad and my mom…
I also have a younger brother and sister.
They all…
help me out a lot.
My parents look after my child
while I go to work.
Do you ever think about
doing something for your parents?
Yeah, I've been thinking that
since I was in middle school.
Like, um…
Wait a minute.
That's a good joke.
It's cute, but…
I want to build a house,
just for my dad and mom.
I've been thinking about it for a while.
I started running a bar
when I was only 24 years old,
but I left home earlier
when I was about 20.
After I left home,
I didn't go back for three or four years.
I didn't even reach out to my parents.
My dad was super strict too,
so he was always on my case,
and I thought it was annoying.
I was just partying all the time,
and then I started running a bar.
I was working part-time at first.
I was surviving out in the world
on my own,
no money for the train,
no home to go back to.
All I could do was try to earn money,
living day to day.
But after I'd spent some time
living like that,
I don't know when, but at some point,
I remembered how strict my dad was,
and I thought, "Oh, okay. Maybe this is
what he was trying to prepare me for."
I thought it was annoying back then, but…
now, I am so grateful
that my dad was strict with me.
My parents raised me
so that I wouldn't get lost
when I was out in the real world.
At that time, I realized
how grateful I was to my parents.
So I contacted them
and ended up going back home.
I made sure to face my parents, properly.
You know, I think that your parents
want you to rely on them in some ways too.
So I don't think that you need to feel bad
about letting them help you at all.
I think words of gratitude
would be enough.
But it's super nice that your parents
get to see their grandchild more.
- More than just nice.
- Yeah, I'm sure they're happy.
They definitely are.
But your mom also had you young, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- She might understand.
- I think your mom will know how you feel.
Mmm. But, like,
my mom did everything by herself.
- So cool.
- All of it. Yeah.
She raised three kids by herself.
- You can make that your goal.
- Right.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Mmm.
- Let's work toward that.
- You're right.
I think it's very admirable
that she chose to have her baby so young.
I don't think I could have
made that choice if I were in her shoes.
We're the same age,
so I thought that was cool.
Write your names
with your butts, let's go!
- This is the worst!
- Yeah, you two can do it together.
- Write "Kahochi" with your butts.
- Seriously?
At the same time. Come on, it'll be fun.
And say it out loud as well.
- Okay, here we go.
- Ready, and--
Ka…
They're the same age.
- So they get along.
- Nice, nice.
- Too much.
- That's so funny.
Rinrin, what is that supposed to be?
- Okay, beautifully done.
- Hey, that was great.
Nice work, girls.
What was that at the end?
We transitioned from Ethics class
to butt-writing.
Getting arrested is no joking matter.
This is a very serious thing
that happened to her.
I'm sure it was tough for her,
and she probably feels guilty
for causing trouble for those around her.
I'm sure it was tough
for those around her too.
Yeah.
So she must have a lot
of determination now,
after going through all that.
Hmm. That's so true.
When they tell their stories,
they always get upset
- and end up crying.
- They do.
It makes me feel like
taking that time to share is important.
I gotta say,
I'm such a big fan of this Ethics class.
- I like it too.
- I like it a lot.
- Nagano is the only one laughing.
- I'm so sorry.
That's annoying. I'm annoyed with myself.
LOUNGE
They're all here already.
- Oh, there it is.
- Hey.
I'll sit next to Maru.
Oh, coming through.
- Okay, let's go.
- When is this gonna start?
Here it comes.
Today,
the men will compete against each other
for a chance to invite a girl
on an overnight date.
Of course. Yes.
After the competition,
they will immediately leave
for their overnight date
to get to know each other better.
All the men, please change
into your swimsuits at this time.
- Swimsuits?
- Will they swim?
The battle will take place on the beach.
- Bring it on.
- Okay, the beach.
- I'm cool with that. That'll be fun.
- Let's do this! Let's go change.
- Wonder what they'll do.
- Bring it on!
- Let's do this.
All right, let's do this!
- Let's give it our all.
- All right, let's go!
What's this?
- A tournament bracket?
- No way.
Is this a tournament?
The battle on the sand
for an overnight date is…
beach flags.
- Beach flags.
- Yay!
- All right!
- I'll win!
- Here it comes!
- Victory is mine!
- Let's go.
- It'll be easy.
Beach flags.
Ladies, you will now decide
on what the match-ups will be
for the guys.
- How about this, this, and then this?
- For these two to go first? Yeah
- It's good right?
- Oh, yeah, that works.
- So that's it?
- Okay.
- Wow!
- Okay!
- So gonna win.
- Everyone wants me to win!
- All right, guys.
- Don't be silly.
First round, Ryopi and Kazuma!
All right!
My time has come!
- Sara, watch me.
- So sweet.
Okay, here we go.
Ready…
- Go!
- Let's go!
- Go for it! You can do it!
- Go!
What the heck?
Ryopi is awesome!
Amazing!
- That's amazing.
- All right!
That was fast.
Running's super hard.
Round two, Maru and me.
- Let's go!
- Yay! You can do it!
This time, I'm going to show you
what I'm made of.
- Yay!
- Here we go. Let's race!
- Maru, do your best.
- Yes!
I'm going to take the last date.
Yay!
- Rune, do your best too.
- Go!
- Okay, referee, please.
- Okay.
- Put your chins down first.
- Ready? Here we go.
Ready, go!
- Maru's catching up.
- Look at that!
- He's fast.
- He's so fast!
- I'm so frustrated.
- Rune is amazing.
Rune works out.
He's in different shape than the others.
Third round, Tai-chan and Kamaken!
- Tai-chan looks fast too.
- They both look fast.
- Kamaken.
- Yeah?
- You can't beat me.
- There you go, Tai-chan.
Okay, Kamaken, you got this.
You doing that the whole race?
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- Both of you?
Here we go.
Ready, go!
Look at Tai-chan!
- It's close.
- Who won?
- Good race.
- That was great!
Why are you always like this?
Seriously!
Give me something to feel happy about.
At least just once.
- Amazing.
- Incredible!
- So fast.
- That was a good race, right?
- Everyone's fast.
- Tai-chan was just as fast.
- They're all so fast.
- Both were amazing.
Wow, that was a close race.
We chose the order perfectly.
- This is the final race.
- Yeah, last one.
- The final race.
- Final three.
Mimi, we'll go if I win.
- Wow.
- Nice.
I'll show you
what your elder is capable of.
- Do your best.
- Yes.
Okay.
I have not been serious
up to this point in the race, but now…
I'm going to be so serious this time!
Here we go. On your marks,
get set…
go!
- Go!
- Let's go!
- Come on, come on, come on!
- Wow, no way.
Again.
Amazing.
- Jeez, he's fast.
- He won so easily.
- So fast. Good job, guys.
- I lost.
Wow, he was fast.
- That was a great race.
- I am not doing well.
Congrats.
The person I choose to go
on an overnight date with is…
Mimi.
- Will you join me?
- Yes, I will.
Are you being bashful?
- See you tomorrow then.
- See you tomorrow?
- Yeah, see you tomorrow.
- He's right.
- Have fun.
- Bye-bye.
I am super excited.
Mmm, I mean, to be honest, I have no idea
how the overnight date will actually go,
but I hope we can deepen
our relationship more.
If we can sleep together, I'd like that.
Well, I'm happy to be chosen.
I'm not unhappy that I was chosen,
but I kinda have
mixed feelings about it all.
For me, when Tai-chan lost the race,
I was like…
Kind of like, "I'm disappointed."
Maybe I was charmed
by how adorable he looked when he lost
and how he let his emotions show.
Now that I think about it,
maybe it felt awkward when he lost
because I was starting to like him.
Yesterday's ranking was Rune, and then…
Tai-chan.
That's what I thought, but, mmm…
What?
- Seriously? That happens?
- You don't understand a thing.
- It happens, yes.
- But this guy!
- Tai-chan, let's go back.
- Come on.
What? Tai-chan…
- Tai-chan, it's time to go.
- That's such a beautiful back.
I seriously messed up.
I'm in shock.
- Look at the way he's sitting.
- Like a sidecar.
You're not riding in a sidecar right now!
I mean, since I was in Part 1 as well,
I experienced how upsetting
the overnight dates can be,
and how everything could totally… change.
Plus, come on,
like, Mimi had to be the one
chosen for the date?
I mean, I was planning on kissing her.
I was planning
to turn everything around today.
But, you know,
I have some other strategies too.
BADLY IN LOVE
MARINE ACADEMY
I could barely fit all my stuff in here.
- Oh, yeah?
- Wait, hold on, just a second there, guys.
- I want to talk to Mimi for a second.
- You want to talk?
Do you mind? Just for a bit, okay?
- Same for you, Maru?
- Yeah, I want a quick word as well.
- Here.
- Hmm? What's this?
- Wear it if you get cold.
- Oh, thank you.
- There's a letter in there.
- Thanks.
- I'd be happy if you read it.
- You got it.
- Oh, he's proactive.
- Let's go.
My feelings for you won't change.
Thank you.
So, you know, I know I started
talking to you on the first day,
and every day since then.
I trust that you see me for who I am.
- And what I felt on the first day…
- Mmm-hmm?
…I will do my best
to keep expressing that right to the end.
- Yeah.
- That's enough.
You lost, so just chill till we get back.
- I did lose the race.
- So then…
- Just the race.
- Wait, then we'll be back.
That's it.
I'm giving this to you too.
I want to lose track of time.
- Okay.
- Here.
- Thank you.
- We'll talk again tomorrow.
- I'll be waiting.
- Yeah, me too.
Okay, I see.
- See you, Mimi.
- So that's how it is.
- See you.
- Sounds good.
- Let's go.
- I'm off.
Bye.
Wow, this is something.
We can't even tell what it's like inside.
No.
Wow, it looks so luxurious.
Oh, here it is.
- Oh, wow.
- What's it like?
- It's so beautiful.
- Oh, wow, so stylish.
So cool.
Totally different
from the loud vibe at school.
- Yeah.
- Loud. Chaotic, even.
Oh, wow, check out this bathtub.
We bathe here?
Such a distance from the bath
to the shower.
Wow, but it's so beautiful.
- It's so nice.
- Hey, it's a pool.
- Is it cold?
- Amazing. It has to be cold.
- I bet is.
- Oh, it's warm.
- Really? It is?
- Because it's cold outside.
This is nice.
- I want to sit.
- Let's sit.
- Okay, cheers!
- Okay.
I was worried for a moment
about what was going to happen.
Why?
Well, I mean, in my mind,
- I could only think about being here.
- Hmm.
- On this date.
- Mmm.
So, like, I thought it would be so lame
if I couldn't go.
And yesterday, in the kitchen,
I said, "Let's go on an overnight date."
- Mmm, you did say that.
- I said I was going to win.
I thought it'd be so lame
if I made that bold claim and lost.
Things with the girls are kind of tense.
It's not like
we're fighting over the guys,
but there's still some awkwardness
between us.
It's kind of tough. Do the guys have that?
- You don't, right?
- Hmm.
- We don't, but also, like…
- They're pretty chill.
For a while,
I thought that everyone was chill.
But I realized that wasn't the case
when you and I were leaving today.
For real, I didn't like it.
I'm not happy about that at all.
I mean, when we had a fair fight
in front of everyone,
they said, "We fought like men,
so I will not go back on my word."
We shook hands,
thanking each other for the race.
- And they came back again? It was weird.
- Yeah.
- If they were actually rooting for us…
- Mmm.
…they wouldn't have given you that stuff,
and try to use it as a tool
to wedge us a part.
Totally unnecessary.
Seriously. I would never do that.
If I lost, I'd would just go into my room,
and keep to myself.
- You know what I mean?
- Mmm-hmm.
It is what it is.
So I think I'll talk about that
when I get back.
Okay, I see. Yeah.
Now, it's time to get ready
for the locals' thank-you party.
Okay, we'll work on the bench.
Oh, this is great.
It was Rune's idea to make
this bench for the locals, remember that?
- Oh, yeah! I see, yeah.
- Oh, nice.
- Once I start, I can't stop.
- It's hot.
I need gloves.
Wow, that's nice. At this rate, we could
probably make three of these benches.
You bet we can.
I wonder how far they've gotten.
- What do you mean?
- The overnight.
Honestly, I was about to cry
in that moment.
I was so frustrated.
I wish there was another chance
to go on a date.
This is excruciating.
Why would you say that
in front of Sharan, Tai-chan?
It's almost like he's doing it on purpose.
Do I drink a lot?
- Do you think I drink a lot?
- I think you do.
- Hey.
- But I'm having fun.
Am I different
from the girls you've met so far?
- You probably drink the most.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- I see.
- I'm not really interested in clothes.
- Mmm-hmm.
My mom was.
I mean, my mom is super interested
in clothes and fashion,
and what to wear, all that.
- So she buys all my clothes.
- Oh, nice.
I went through a lot of tough times
when I was young, because of my mom.
- Mmm-hmm.
- When I was in elementary school,
I would come home in the evening--
- No, no, in the afternoon.
- Mmm…
And at the time, I could never figure out
why she was always in such a terrible mood
when I got home.
I was like, "Why do I have to be
so careful around her?"
Now that I work in nightlife, I understand
how hard it must have been for her.
I can understand that now.
We still fight, but I also depend on her
for a lot of things.
Mmm.
Yeah. I love my mom.
- That's nice.
- I don't want to be like my mom, though.
I want to be an even more
attractive woman than her.
Since last year,
my job has finally settled down a bit,
so we can go on trips together,
and that kind of stuff.
And we're finally going to go
on our first overseas trip together soon.
- That'll be fun.
- That's nice.
You know, I just…
I love my mom. So much.
I really do.
Mmm.
Now that I'm an adult, I can understand
how hard she was working to raise me
while also working at night.
I think she wanted to enjoy being a woman,
and not just a mom.
Because she is more than just a mother.
The fact is,
I had clothes to wear, food to eat,
and I had a roof over my head.
The biggest thing is that
she sent me to a good school,
which costs a lot of money.
She did all that for me.
I realized as an adult that she worked
so hard to be able to take care of me.
That hit me pretty hard. I mean…
Back then, I thought it was kind of cool
to pretend not to understand things,
even if I actually did.
But now,
I think that what I did
was actually just lame.
The more I thought about it,
the more I realized
that I was a pretty lame kid.
Mmm.
- I wanted to win so bad.
- I wanted you to win too.
You know, if I had won today…
I'm just gonna say it.
Straight up.
- Come on, look at me.
- What is it?
I would have chosen you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
That makes me smile.
- You rooted for me? No way.
- Yeah, I did.
Yeah, I was like, "Yes!" in my heart.
- Oh, when I won?
- Yeah.
- The first round?
- Mmm.
But it was a close race.
- Did you see it? When I got it?
- I saw it.
Oh, you did?
I don't know how many years it's been
since I ran that hard.
- Was my running kind of weird?
- Not at all.
It wasn't?
Everything you do looks cool.
- Oh, she said it!
- Cute.
Really?
- Oh, man! Kamaken is adorable.
- He's totally smitten.
I feel like things have changed a lot
since we went on that date.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah, yeah, for sure.
I think it's fun to talk with you,
and I feel like
I can be myself around you.
- Oh, really?
- Absolutely. For sure.
So when we were walking
on the beach earlier,
I was thinking to myself,
"If I go with anyone, it'll be Rinrin."
Hey, you're not talking at all today.
Rinrin.
Look at those eyes. She's so cute!
- My heart's fluttering all over the place.
- So cute!
His face, his movement,
everything about him is cool.
I love it.
Rune, what about taking a bath?
- The bath?
- We need to bathe.
- Rune, you go first.
- Okay.
- Since I take so long.
- Yeah.
- Like, now?
That's better, right? If we do that,
I could take my makeup off
and drink later if we're going to.
- So let's take our baths now.
- I'll go take one.
He's been pretty cool-headed
up till now, right?
What's happening?
Dear Mimi,
In Part 1, I saw an overnight date
change everything.
I wanted to win and take you on a date,
but I failed.
Even though that dream is dead,
I'll work hard for both of us!
The distance and our ages don't matter.
I'll show you my love in my own way!
My writing sucks,
but my feelings are true. Taisei
I received a letter and clothes
from Tai-chan.
Maru struggled to find something too,
and he handed me his watch.
Like, I think those gestures
had an impact on me.
Even when…
I was talking to Rune,
in the back of my mind,
it's not like they were there,
but I was thinking about the two of them.
And a part of me
felt kind of bad for them.
I wanted to focus, but my brain
was kind of all over the place.
So, like, Tai-chan gave me that letter
before we left, and I read it.
Mmm.
- I just wanted to let you know.
- Mmm. What did you think?
- Hmm, I thought it was cute.
- Mmm.
I can't help but think
that he's adorable. It's like…
I don't want to keep any secrets from you.
- So, you know, the day before…
- Mmm.
…it was when we all had
that one-on-one time
to talk with each other,
Maru told me
he was going to try hard for me,
and Tai-chan said he'd do his best too.
So, of course,
I was watching the tournament
- with all of that running through my mind.
- Mmm.
But in the end, I'd have no idea
if someone would choose me
until it happens.
They can say they'll choose me,
- but I don't know for sure.
- Mmm.
And I'm a pretty
skeptical person after all.
And, I don't know,
especially because of
this whole environment we're in,
where we have six girls, it's six and six.
I didn't want a guy to be thinking,
"I hope I end up
with the best of these six."
You're being very clear about things,
and about what you feel.
And, like, I wasn't thinking I'd pick you
just because you were the best
out of the six.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- I thought you maybe felt that way.
- Honestly, I feel like…
Whether it was 6 girls or 100,
it honestly wouldn't have changed
anything for me.
I felt the flutter.
My voice is flat,
so it might not sound like I mean it.
But that's how I truly feel.
I wouldn't have asked you out today
if I didn't mean it.
I'm happy to hear that.
Mmm.
There's two beds. How should we sleep?
This is where it starts.
They can't just keep talking forever.
- That's right.
- It's too romantic.
How are we going to sleep?
Are you okay with one each?
If you want to sleep separately,
that's totally fine.
Or we could sleep in the same bed.
You're going to sleep next to me?
Yeah.
Are you tired?
I wonder if we can sleep.
At this point,
I feel like it's a waste to sleep.
Oh, wow!
What's with this super grainy footage?
It's like there's a horizontal line
that's censoring what's happening.
That was good.
- They chose the bed.
- It makes you imagine things
- in the pitch black with the lights off.
- That's excellent.
I wonder how this is going to go.
- Well, she said she felt a flutter.
- Yeah.
- She said that. But who knows?
- Oh, right.
It's not like how Ayacheru was.
- Yeah, it's not "Thanksies."
- Right. "Thanksies."
- It's not that.
- Not like that.
Not "thanksies" at all.